# Shikirra Williams

Atlanta, GA

678.315.6619 shikirra.williams@gmail.com github.com/shikirra12 linkedin.com/in/shikirrawilliams

### SUMMARY

I'm a diligent and ambitious learner with great adaptability. I learn best through working with peers, researching, and hands-on experience, and I've perfected this approach in my passion for coaching individuals on new skills. Now that I've learned Java, I'm ready to take on new challenges in tech!

#### SKILLS

Java
Spring
IntelliJ w/ Debugger
Test Driven Development
JavaScript
Node.JS
HTML
CSS
Git
GitHub

### RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

## The Iron Yard | Atlanta, GA Aug 2017 - Oct 2017 Back-end Engineering with Java Program

The Iron Yard is a 12-week coding bootcamp specializing in highly focused, immersive training centered on language fluency, object-oriented programming, and project-based learning.

- CanlGetUhh
  - Created a restful API using Java, to allow customers to create a drink queue and send orders to a bartender
- Gabble
  - Created a social media platform that employed Sequelize as the database using JavaScript
- Itunes Music Search
  - Utilized a fetch call to iTunes' API to gather and display artist name and song information. Used HTML, CSS, and JavaScript

### Uncle Julio's | Sandy Springs, GA 2015 - 2017 Front of House Manager

Uncle Julio's serves higher end Tex-Mex cuisine with their own twist on traditional platters and hosts an array of large parties. This experience taught me about time management, delegating tasks, and learning by trial and error.

 Solved complaints, addressed customer issues, and triaged guest needs with available resources

### Twin Peaks | Atlanta, GA Trainer/Bartender

2014 - 2015

Twin Peaks is a fast-paced sports bar with themed outfits that offers multiple parties for large often sports-related groups and events. This experience taught me how to manage large groups of people and shaped my critical and decision making skills.

- Presented 25 orientation and training sessions ranging in size from 7-50 new employees
- Constantly researched and learned new skills in order to train new employees on the latest techniques and best prepare them for success

#### Education

### Georgia State University Completed 45 credit hours